Martin P. Catherwood Library Librarian's Office Additional Files /4272
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Martin P. Catherwood Library Librarian's Office Additional Files
1948- 2005
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
Martin P. Catherwood Library
Miller, J. Gormly
Harper, Shirley
Law, Gordon T., Jr.
/4272
12.5 cubic feet
12 linear ft.
Records (documents).
8072259
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, May 28, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 05, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4272 P: Martin P. Catherwood Library Librarian's Office Photographs
Miller, J. Gormly; Harper, Shirley F.; Law, Gordon T., Jr.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations; Martin P. Catherwood Library. Librarian's Office.; Martin P. Catherwood Library.
8072259
- Accreditation and reaccreditation 100.10 Cornell, April 01, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Cornell Self-study for Middle States Reaccreditation, 2001 110.40.90 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Distance Learning Approval Program 110.40.90.40, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Dullea, Hank 110.50, 1998-2001 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- eCornell Agreement with Unit for Program 110.60, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Office of Distance Learning 140.80, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Rawlings, Hunter R. III 160, 1994-2005 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Rethinking SUNY, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- SUNY Report 230 (Folder 1 of 2), 1996-2004 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- SUNY Report 230 (Folder 2 of 2), 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- SUNY Statistical Release 260, 1990-1998 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- ARL Preservation Statistics 300.80.40, 1991-1998 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Cooperative Resource Allocation 310.10, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Core AG Project at Mann 310.20, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Cornell Assist (Mann) 310.40, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- CTS Cataloging Review: 1994 320.20 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- CUL Annual Report, Narrative 320.50.80 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- CUL Annual Statistics, Final Report, 1971-1993 320.60.10 (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 18)
- CUL Annual Statistics, Final Report, 1971-1993 320.60.10 (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 19)
- CUL Annual Statistics, Final Report, 1994-1999 320.60.20 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Digital Library 330.20, 1996-1999 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- InfoShare 330.30, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Library Management System 330.30.50, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- OCLC Prism 340.40.80 (Folder 1 of 3), 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- OCLC Prism 340.40.80 (Folder 2 of 3), 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- OCLC Prism 340.40.80 (Folder 3 of 3), 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Planning CUL's Digital Future, 10 January 00 340.60.10, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- RLG/RLIN 360, 1994-2004 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- RLIN Tape Products and Services 360.20, 1990-1993 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Message Points for ILR 400.70.10, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Faculty Memoranda 430.20, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Faculty Research and Publications 430.40, 1989-1998 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Fiftieth (50th) Anniversary of I.L.R. School 430.80, 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Global HR in Transition: ILR 651, Harry Katz. Spring 2001 430.90 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- International Initiative 440.60, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Junket Ideas 440.60.20, 1990-2001 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- New York City Educational and Research Initiative 440.70.20, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Occasional Letter from the Dean, E. Lawler, 1998- 440.70.40 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- School Mission Statement, 1988 440.80.30 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Bunge Survey 500.70, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Performance Data for Catherwood, 1945-1980 540.30.30, 1945-1990 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Special Report, Catherwood, 1960-1980 560.30 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Admin. Computing Committee (ILR) 600.40, 1994-1998 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Catherwood Grants Committee 600.60, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Catherwood Public Relations 600.70, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Operate an Electronic Publishing (Priority Objective #7, Spring 05) 620.80, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Uris Information Technology Center Committee, 1999 680 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Approval Plan 800.40.40, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Collecting Inspection and Furbishing Project, 1985 810.10 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Collection Size 810.10.20, 1986-2002 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Coordinated Collection Development (CCD) 1990-99 810.20.10 (Folder 1 of 2), 1996-1998 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Coordinated Collection Development (CCD) 1990-99 810.20.10 (Folder 2 of 2), 1991-1995 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Coordinated Collection Development (CCD) 1980-89 810.20.20 (Folder 1 of 2), 1983-1989 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Coordinated Collection Development (CCD) 1980-89 810.20.20 (Folder 2 of 2), 1981-1985 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- CUL: Task Force on Electronic Journal 810.30, 1993-1998 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- 19th Century Monograph Project 1999 840.20.40 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- RLG Conspectus 850, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Amazon Contract 900.10.10, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Electronic Resources (no longer current) 910.10, 1981-2003 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Project Agreements 1984-2000 960 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Computing Hardware at Catherwood 1000.80, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- EZ-Remote 1010.90, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Global Crossing 1020.20 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Hardware Projections For Cathewood, 1998 1020.60, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- NUBB (Network Usage Based Billing) 1040.70, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Network (Catherwood) 1040.40, 1994-1996 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Internet Training Project 1220, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Internet Training Project (Catherwood) 1220 (Folder 1 of 2), 1997 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Internet Training Project (Catherwood) 1220 (Folder 2 of 2), 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Rate Structure for Home Page Design 1260, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- SHRM/HRIN Joint Venture 1270 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- La Tourelle Advance, 17 March 97 1320.40 (Folder 1 of 2), 1997 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- La Tourelle Advance, 17 March 97 1320.40 (Folder 2 of 2), 1997 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- University Strategic Planning, 1994 1380 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Vision Statement (includes, Executive Summary, Mission, Goals, and Objectives) 1390, 1995-2003 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Building Celebration, 18 October 02 1400.10, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Scope and Contents
  Contains photographs of the celebration
- Building Dedication, April '98 1400.20 (Folder 1 of 2), 1998 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Building Dedication, April '98 1400.20 (Folder 2 of 2), 1998 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Construction (1997) 1400.80, 1997-1999 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Construction (1995) 1410.20, 1994-1998 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Construction (1994) 1410.30 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Construction (1993) 1410.40 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Construction (1993) 1410.40 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Construction Calaender 1410.70, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Floor Plans, Phase I and II (detailed full size mechanic drawings available through Kheel Center) 1420.10 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Groundbreaking, 4 May 00 1420.20.80, 1993-2003 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Interim Renovations- Photos (1985-92) (archived 10/06) 1420.80.20, 1985-1992 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  Folder moved to another location
- Master Plan (Phase I) 1430, 1988-1993 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Master Plan (Phase II) 1430.50, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Master Plan (Phase II) 1430.50 (Folder 1 of 2), 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Master Plan (Phase II) 1430.50 (Folder 2 of 2), 1991-1997 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Master Planning Input 1430.60, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Phase II: Audio Visual/Distance Learning 1440.30.90.10, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Naming Opportunities for the New Building 1994 1440.20, 1994-1999 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Phase II: Construction, 2000 1440.40, 2000-2002 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  Contains photographs
- Phase II: Furniture/ Interior Finishes 1440.50, 1998-2003 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Phase II Rehab Planning, 1993 1440.60, 1994-1999 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Relocation/ Surge Prep for Phase II, 1999 1460.40 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Signage: Phase I, 9/97- 1470.20.40, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Middle Class 1630.20 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Integrity, The Keystone for University Stewardship 1730.60, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- IRRA: Atlanta, 3-6 January 02 1720.60.70, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- IRRA: Boston, 6-9 January 00 1720.60.80, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- IRRA: NYC, 3-5 January 99 1720.60.90, 1996-1999 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Labor Issues Caucus 1730.10.90, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- McKersie Festschrift, 30-31 October 98, Cambridge, MA 1730.30, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- SLA: Minneapolis, 5-10 June 1999 1740.60.70 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- SLA: Indianapolis 7-12, 1998 1740.60.80 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- SUNY Council of Library Directors, Bolton Landing, 18-20 April 01 1760.40.80, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- SUNY Council of Library Directors: Bolton Landing, NY, 5-7 April 00 1760.40.90, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- SUNY Council of Library Directors: Bolton Landing, NY, 28-30 April 99 1760.50, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- The Future for Librarians: 1780 Position Yourself for Success, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Trademark Registration 1800.80, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Aga Kahn Foundation 1900.10.50, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Associates Program 1900.40, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- BNA Sponsorship of Web Site 1900.50, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Buffalo, 28 June 01 1900.50.10, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Catherwood Advisory Council: NYC, 14 October 99 1910.30.90, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Catherwood Advisory Council: NYC, 21 April 99 1910.40, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Catherwood Advisory Council: NYC, 28 October 98 1910.40.10, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Catherwood Advisory Council :Ithaca, 17 April 98 1910.40.20, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Catherwood Advisory Council: NYC, 27 October 97 1910.40.30, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Catherwood Advisory Council: NYC, 28 April 97 1910.40.40, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Catherwood Advisory Council: NYC, 7 November 96 1910.40.50, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Catherwood Advisory Council: NYC, 27 March 96 1910.40.60, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Catherwood Advisory Council: NYC, 15 November 95 1910.40.70, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Catherwood Advisory Council: 1910.40.80 NYC, 15 June 95, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Catherwood Advisory Council: 1910.40.90 Ithaca, 22 April 95, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Catherwood Advisory Council Meeting Planning for Spring 1995 Meeting 1910.50, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Chicago: 24-26 May 00 1920.70.70, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Chicago Community Trust 1920.70.70.10, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Cornell/ BNA Information Day, 1994 1930 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Cornell/CMP Foundation Partnership 1930.10, 1986-1997 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Donations/Gifts, 1980-1999 1930.10.60 (Folder 1 of 2), 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Donations/Gifts, 1980-1999 1930.10.60 (Folder 2 of 2), 1990-1995 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Dean's Advisory Council Via Pic Tel 6 April 95 1930.20, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Dean's Dinner, Trustee Council Weekend, 9 October 99 1930.30, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Eclipse Publications and Industrial Relations Services from Michael Rubinstein 1930.70.20, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Endowments 1930.80, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Fundraising, 1982-1991 1940.30.50 (Folder 1 of 2), 1988-1990 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Fundraising, 1982-1991 1940.30.50 (Folder 2 of 2), 1983-1989 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Fundraising, 1982-1991 1940.30.50 (Folder 2 of 2), 1983-1989 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- ILR Building Campaign, Phase II 1940.70.50, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Indianapolis/ Chicago/ Indy 500: 27 May 04 to 1 June 04 1940.80.10, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Indianapolis: 23-28 May 02 1940.80.20, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Information Institute Proposal 1960, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Invitations to ILR to Partner on the Web 1960.10.10, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Kahn Project to Enrich Lais 1960.30, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Kheel Book Reception, 13-14 May 99, New York 1960.30.20.10, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- McPherson, James 1960.30.50.60, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Milwaukee, 6 December 99 1960.30.60.10, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Neufeld, Maurice 1960.40.10, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- New York 19-20 March 01 (Konvitz Luncheon) 1960.60.70, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- New York: 1-3 December 99: Kheel Holiday Party 1960.0.10.90, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- New York: 7-8 July 98 1960.60.20.10, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- New York: 1-3 June 98 1960.60.20.20, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- New York Washington, 16-19 November 99 (Weingarten Reception) 1960.60.60.10, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- PERC Foundation 1960.90, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Rochester, NY: 22-23 August 02 (Xerox Lunch) 1970.40.90, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Salk Institute 1970.50.20, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Septimus, Alan 1970.60.10.20, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Space and Plaque (Phase Iia) Commitment 1970.60.40.60, 2001-2004 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Telecommunications and Information Infrastructure Assistance Program 1970.80, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Toronto, 19-21 May 99 1990.30.80, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Trustee Council Defined 1990.30.90, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Trustees Council, 26 October 00 1990.40.30.80, 1998-2000 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Van Arsdale Proposal 1990.40.40, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Washington, 14-15 March 95 1990.70, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- White Plains: 6-7 February 03 1990.70.40.40, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Acquisitions Budget Picture Developed for Dean Lawler, May 00 2000.20, 1994-2000 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Budget Cuts: FY 96 2000.40, 1993-1995 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Budget Cuts: FY 00 2000.50, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Budget Cuts: FY94-FY04 2000.50.30, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Budget Shortfalls for Acquisitions, 1990-2002 2000.50.60 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Catherwood Budget: FY04 2000.50.60.90, 2003-2004 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Catherwood Budget: FY 03 2000.50.70, 2001-2003 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Catherwood Budget: FY 02 2000.50.80, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Catherwood Budget: FY 01 2000.50.90, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Catherwood Budget; FY 00 2000.60 (Folder 1 of 2), 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Catherwood Budget; FY 00 2000.60 (Folder 2 of 2), 1999 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Catherwood Budget: FY 99 2000.70, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Catherwood Budget: FY 98 2000.80, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Catherwood Budget: FY 97 2000.90, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- CUL Budget Report through 2004 2010.10, 1989-2004 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Model of Acquisitions Shortfall, 1990-2002 2040 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- State Budget Cuts, FY85-FY94 2060, 1988-1995 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- SUNY Budget Information 2070, 2000-2004 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- SUNY Budget Requests 2080, 1994-1999 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Merchant Statements Summary of Bankcard Deposits and Daily Credit Card Deposits for Catherwood Library, 1997-1999 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Accounts Receivable, 1995-1999 2100.20 (Folder 1 of 2), 1995-2003 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Accounts Receivable, 1995-1999 2100.20 (Folder2 of 2), 1995-2001 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Documents Relating to Bank Accounts and Cred Cards with Catherwood Library (Folder 1 of 2), 2003-2005 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Documents Relating to Bank Accounts and Cred Cards with Catherwood Library (Folder 2 of 2), 1997-2003 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Documents Relating to Banking and the Kheel Center (Fold12 1 of 2), 2001-2003 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Documents Relating to Banking and the Kheel Center (Folder 2 of 2), 2002 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Accounts Receivable, 2000-2004 2100.20 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Automation Funds 2100.40 (Folder 1 of 2), 1991-2003 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Automation Funds 2100.40 (Folder 2 of 2), 1985-1991 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Fiscal Reporting 2100.80.70 2100.80.70, 1989-2001 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Fiscal Year 01/02 2110.40.80, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Fiscal Year 00/01 2110.40.90, 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Fiscal Year 99/00 2110.50, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Fiscal Year 98/99 2110.50.10, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Fiscal Year 97/98 2110.50.20, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Fiscal Year 96/97 2110.50.30, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Fiscal Year 95/96 2110.50.40, 1995-1997 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Fiscal Year 94/95 2110.50.50, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Fiscal Year 93/94 2110.50.60, 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Fiscal Year 92/93 2110.50.70, 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Fiscal Year 91/92 2110.50.80, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Fiscal Year 90/91 2110.50.90, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- 501-3315-599 2110.60 Founders' Oral History Project, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- 513-3701 2110.70 Finance Guide to Info Resources on Employment Relations in the U.S., 1990-1992 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- 515-3704 2110.70.20 LMDC/ NYPL Microfilming Project, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- 515-3716 2110.70.50 Local Labor Union Video, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- NYU Van Arsdale Labor History Documentation Project 515-8705 2110.80.40 (Folder 1 of 2), 2001-2003 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- NYU Van Arsdale Labor History Documentation Project 515-8705 2110.80.40 (Folder 2 of 2), 1998-2001 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- 515-8707 2110.80.50 Brettschieder Memorial Book Endow, 1979-1986 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- 515-8712 2110.80.80 Konvitz Papers, 1984-1995 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- 515-8713-707 2110.80.90 Stein Papers, 1990-1992 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- 515-8718 2110.90.10 Preservation Conservation of Hist Photographic Materials Grant, 1988-1992 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- 515-8719 2110.90.20 RLG Archives Preservation, 1990-1995 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Golden Account to Fund "YWCA Exhibit" 2120.10, 1994-1995 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- ILR Fiscal Outlook, 1995 2120.40 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Insurance 2120.80, 1998-2001 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Cornell Univ. Invested Fund Statements Catherwood Libr Periodical Endow, 1998-2002 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Invested Fund Statements, (prior 10 2002) 2130 (Folder 1 of 2), 1990-2001 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Invested Fund Statements, (prior 10 2002) 2130 (Folder 2 of 2), 1985-1987 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Preservation of Photo Materials Project 2150.20, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Classification Review Study and Raises, 1993 2200.60, 1993-1995 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Customer Training 2210, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Diversity in the Classroom: Faculty Student Interaction, 20 September 01 2210.10, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Effort Analysis 2210.30 (Folder 1 of 3), 2001 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Effort Analysis 2210.30 (Folder 2 of 3), 1991-1997 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Effort Analysis 2210.30 (Folder 3 of 3), 1990-1992 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Performance Dialogue: Manual, January 1999-2000 2260.10 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Retirement Legislation, New York State A.3128 and S.1828 (1995) 2260.60 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Rewards and Incentives, 1997 2260.60.40 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Roadmap Syllabus 2260.80, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Salary Program History thru 1999 2260.80.10, 1993-2001 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Total Quality Management 2280.60, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Temporary Appointments, 1991-2002 2280.40 (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Temporary Appointments, 1991-2002 2280.40 (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Card Pulling Project 2300.30 from ILR Card Catalog, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Minimal Level Cataloging 2300.40, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Online Catalog in Distributed Environment 2340, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Outsourcing Cataloging 2340.10, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Reorganization, 1994 2340.60 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Technical Services 2370, 1992-2002 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Teach Team 1992-1994 2370.40 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Canadian Center for Occupational and Safety: Hamilton, Ontario 2400.60, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Document Delivery, 1993-96 2410.40, 1993-1996 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Fee Based Services, 1995 2410.60 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Purdue Technical Information Service, 1995 2440.20 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Commission on Prevention and Access, 1994 2500.60 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Preservation, 1994-96 2560, 1994-1996 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Census of Information Seeking Patters of ILR Faculty and Staff, Fall 94 2610, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Surveys of Catherwood Library Service (Folder 1 of 2), 1994 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Surveys of Catherwood Library Service (Folder 2 of 2), 1994 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Faculty Survey Responses 2620.40 (Folder 1 of 2), 1994 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Faculty Survey Responses 2620.40 (Folder 2 of 2), 1994 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Post Graduate Survey 2660, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- ICPSR 2820, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Governor's Budget, 1995/96 3020, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- New York State Department of Economic Development 3040 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- New York State Legislative Activity/ Issues 3040.20, 1993-1996 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- New York State Legislature: Committees 3040.40, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Kleinberg, Helen 3800.60, 1996-2002 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Reeves, Don 4600.40, 1998-2004 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Rosen, Ned 4700, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Bronson, Ann, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Connie Buckley, 1993-1998 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Personnel Record- Carroll, Lori, 1989-1991 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Personnel Record: Clark, Valerie, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Personnel Records: Eastman Carol, 1969-1985 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Christina H. Fenn, 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Fisher, Linda, 1999-2000 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Graham, Marianne- Personnel Record, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Personnel Record: Helmer, Stephen, 1991-1996 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Hodges, Martha- Personnel Record 3/17/83- 7/30/92, 1982-1992 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Jenkins, William - Personnel Record, 1995-1997 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Julian, Edward A. - Personnel record, 1989-1992 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Kim, Chung N. Personal Record, 1979-1995 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Koerpel, Gretchen, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Thomas Kottmann, 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Lauderdale, Walter E., 1990 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- LI, Dian- Personnel Record 10/3/91 - 5/22/92, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Lowry, Linda - Personnel Record, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- B. McGinnis (Folder 1 of 2), 2001-2003 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- B. McGinnis (Folder 2 of 2), 1998-2001 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Mclyman, Victoria E. Personnel record 10/26/92 - 04/28/93, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Mersereau, Darcie - Personnel Record 5/27/93 - 8/17/94, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- MOURA, Maria - Personnel File, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Manos, Paulette, 1993-2005 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Tim Murch, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- QUVUS, Deanna - Personnel Record 10/3/88 - 1/31/90, 1988-1990 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- RINCHACK, Patricia - Personnel Record 3/8/90-, 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Schmidt, Hans C. - Personnel record, 1989-1991 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Winder, Patricia Personnel File, 1969-1995 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Zimmerman, Carolyn - Personnel Record, 1967-1993 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- E. Industrial Relations Librarians Committee E-1 General, 1971-1992 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- E. Industrial Relations Librarians Comm. E-3 Lists, 1960-1981 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- CIRL - 1990 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- E - COMM. OF INDUS. RELA. LIBRARIANS E-8 35th Annual Meeting - Cornell University, May 27-29, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- E. Comm. Univ. Industrial Relations Librns. E-8 33rd Annual Meeting - Ontario Ministry, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- E. Comm. Univ. Industrial Relations E-8 26th Annual meeting Librn Cornell Univ. 1972 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- E. Industrial Relations Librarians Comm E-2 Publications Exchange, 1968-1971 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- E. COMM. UNIV. INDUSTRIAL REALTIONS LIBRNS E-8 25th Annual Meeting - Cornell Univ. 1971 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  First three documents on top very wrinkled
- E. COMM. UNIV. INDUSTRIAL RELATIONS LIBRNS E-8 24th Annual Meeting - U. of Mich. June 4-6, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 9)